Hey guys.
Quick check. Quick check.
So how, how are things going on so far?
I hope you have been taking a lot of notes
and really doing the hands-on.
Okay. There's a very famous quote by,
by an American Will Rogers,
even if you are on the right track,
you will get run over if you just sit there.
You are on the right track.
You have bought the course, you are in this course,
but if you don't take the HA steps to really practice,
take notes, share notes,
put down your thoughts in the comments
below, it really won't help.
Okay, let me repeat, even if you're on the right track,
you'll get run over if we just set, set by Will Rogers.
So in this section you're gonna be doing a lot
of hands on a lot of activities you'll do in this section.
Okay? You'll learn about the development lifecycle as well.
You learn about unit testing as well
and the coming few videos.
In fact, I wanted to really evolve in this.
And then towards the end, you know, just reflect on
what I've done so far and then write down
in the last two videos, command
below what you've learned so far.
I want to, and, and this video below,
I really wanna see your commitment.
Okay? So gimme a commitment
and the command below what you gonna do next.
Today, whatcha gonna accomplish? Alright, let's get going.
And, uh, before you go to the next video, comment down
below.